>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们总结一下我们的想法，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
let's summarize our thoughts on,
或者我跟你分享的想法
or my thoughts that I've shared with you,
我想我应该说的是他们不同类型的功能
I guess I should say, on functions
of their various different types.
我认为功能宣言有一些
It is my opinion that function
declarations have some
对他们有优越感
superiority to them.
我们甚至还没谈过那些事我们会回到他们的时候
We haven't even talked about all of those,
we'll come back to those when we get to,
比如说在后面浪费时间
for example, wasting, later.
但是，函数声明对指定的函数表达式有一些好处。
But a function declaration has some
benefits over a named function expression.
但是命名函数表达式对于
But named function expressions
have huge benefits over
匿名函数表达式。
anonymous function expressions.
所以我觉得第二个比前两个要强烈得多，
So I feel much more strongly about the
second two of these than the first two,
尽管我也喜欢命名函数声明
even though I also do tend to prefer
the named function declarations.
所以这才是我们要知道的
So it's just something to be aware of,
因为这不是真的很容易和快速的规则
because this isn't really something
that can be such a hard and fast rule.
你得看看各种不同的情况。
You do have to look at
the various different cases.
我当然明白为什么人们会用箭头
And I certainly understand why
people might use an arrow function
当五个字符翻倍时
when it's five characters
doubling some variable.
但即使在那些你被诱惑去拯救一段时间的情况下
But even in those cases where you're
tempted just to save a little bit of time,
我还是会说名字翻倍
I would still argue that the name,
double it,
比看 X 乘以 2更直接
tells me something more directly
than looking at x times 2.
所以我只想让你考虑更大的目的
So I just want you to consider that
bigger purpose, which is we want to
我们的密码能尽可能有效地沟通哪怕一眼
have our code communicate as effectively
as possible, even at a glance,
不需要有人读和读一些代码
without somebody having to read and
sort of mentally execute some code and
了解它的工作方式，或考虑对其进行任何类型的处理。
figure out what it does, or
consider any sort of corner cases on it.
我们不希望读者要做这些事情，理想的是。
We don't want the reader to have
to do those things, ideally.
我们希望他们能阅读我们的代码
We want them to be able
to read our code and
了解它的目的几乎是一瞥
understand it's purpose
almost at a glance.
因此，这些都是我喜欢按此顺序执行功能的原因，并且
So those are the reasons why I prefer
the functions in this order, and
我会努力工作下去我基本上只会
I would work my way down, and
I would essentially only ever
以箭头表达式形式执行匿名函数表达式。
do the anonymous function expression
in the arrow expression form.
在那个特殊的情况下我只会这样做因为我在做词法
And in that one particular case, I would
only do so because I was getting lexical
单击，稍后我们将会讨论这个问题。
clicks, which we'll talk
about later in the course.